carzoom.in 2018-09-28

# Privacy Policy | Carzoom.in | Car Zoom

Thank you for your interest in CarZoom’s services and privacy info. Please note that our privacy policy doesn’t apply to that information which you already have posted publicly or display on this site. In that case, you kind of grant us a license to all publicly-posted content and it can be display or syndicated to other sites and CarZoom’s partners.

### Information we collect

Without revealing any personal information, one can visit CarZoom any time and use many of its features.

But, in case, if you register with the CarZoom and take part in its various activities like posting a comment, enrolling in a contest then you may be asked to provide your personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, address, contact no. etc along with some non-personally identifiable information like your location, personal & professional interests, age, gender, your experience with CarZoom and its services etc. Also, we may get data about our users from the third parties.

Further, in case, you are connecting with CarZoom via any social networking site like facebook, twitter, linked-in etc then we are free to collect your profile information from that particular site and not liable for the same.

**Note:** We respect our visitors/users rights and support “Right to be forgotten”. If you think you’ve ever shared your contact details with us & want us to remove that info, please contact us at [info@carzoom.in](mailto:info@carzoom.in).

### What about IP addresses?

Like every other website, we may collect and use data contained in log files including your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider i.e. Airtel, Vodafone etc), browser using by you to visit CarZoom (like Google etc), time taken by you to visit CarZoom and also which and how many pages you visited throughout the site.

**How CarZoom use and share the data collected by users?**

We may use the users data in many terms like:

  * To improve our content and services.
  * To give opportunity to our readers to participate in CarZoom-related activities & events.
  * To show/send ads and other contents which we think may be of reader’s interest.
  * To send mails/newsletters related to CarZoom.

We may also share user’s non-identifiable data to the third parties.

However, we do not provide your personal identifiable information to third parties without your approval, except:

  * In the cases of suspected violations or abusive manner/attitude against our terms and policy and in order to investigate and take action regarding the same.
  * With our trusted service providers who assist us in our business operations and also have made us assure of data confidentiality.
  * In case of selling and transferring the site to other company, user’s personal information will be transferred too. Though, we will give you proper notification in that particular case.

### What about ‘Cookies’?

‘Cookies’ are small pieces of information of any website you are visiting which may be stored in your computer’s hard drive. Thus, it may also possible that reader will be served cookies by us, by our advertisers or by that companies which help us delivering  advertising on this site. These cookies help us and advertisers to identify users on our site and on other sites as well.

### Policy updation

We may change or update our Policy from time to time. In case of making any material change in which user’s info will be treated then we will inform you of such changes by updating any tagline like ‘updated privacy policy’ etc. Any updated privacy policy will be come in immediate effect as soon as it is posted on this site.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track visitors on this site. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this data.In order to be compliant with the new regulation Google included a data processing amendment.The data we collect will be processed anonymously and “Data sharing” is disabled.We don’t use other Google services in combination with Google Analytics cookies.

### Contact Us

For getting any further information about CarZoom, please visit ‘[Contact Us](http://carzoom.in/contact-us "Contact Us")’ section.
